Finding Aid for the Recordings of Evenings for New Music, 1964-1980
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Reel to reel tapes not reformatted 1964-1978, II.; Reel 151-162
  - Evenings for New Music Concert at WBAI Free Music Store, February 3 1977, 2 7-inch reels; There is no program accompanying the tapes. Content description is from an original program in the Archive for the Center of the Creative and Performing Arts. The content cannot be confirmed until the tapes are reformatted. (Reel 161-162)
    Satie, Erik
    Socrate
    Performers: Martha Herr-Hanneman, soprano; Nils Vigeland, piano
    Babbitt, Milton, 1916-2011
    Also presented on Evenings for New Music Concert 144, December 11 1976.
    Apartment House 1776 (Chamber version)
    Dmaathen: for oboe and percussion soloists
Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the Library's online catalog.
Subjects
Concerts--New York (State)--Buffalo; Music--20th century
Genres
Sound recordings
Associated Material
Related Resources
Related Resources in the Music Library
Evenings for New Music, 1964-1980 Catalog
An online catalog of the concert performances.
Evenings for New Music, 1964-1980 database
Online searchable database for all the programs (not just the recorded events).
Music Library Special Collections
The Music Library holds several related collections, including paper records of the Center of the Creative and Performing Arts, photographs of events, related personal collections, and audio collections of other contemporaneous concert series.